XAVIER NABAIS



© xavierNabais

☐ xavier-nabais

⟨ +351 915 346 913

☐ xaviernabais0@gmail.com

PROFILE

My name is Xavier and I have been a digital enthusiast since childhood. From an early age, I explored internet browsing and played many games, which allowed me to develop various skills and understand the programming behind them. In addition, I acquired extensive knowledge on how to use websites, as well as a great deal of experience in user interface, easily distinguishing between good and bad user experiences.

WORK EXPERIENCE

□ 03/2017 - 08/2017

Portugal

Shoe Designer

Rokefil

■ During my internship at the company, I worked as a footwear designer and followed the entire process of creating new models, from planning to the final design stamping on the footwear pieces.

■ 03/2018 - 08/2018

Portugal

PHP Software Developer / WordpressCyber1 Group

■ During my internship at the company, I worked as a PHP programmer on a CRUD software, carrying out bug fixing processes and implementing new functionalities. In addition, I also worked as a WordPress developer, creating and developing projects on the platform.

6 03/2019 - 08/2019

Portugal

PHP Web Developer

Cyber1 Group

■ During my internship at the company, I worked as a PHP programmer on a CRUD software, carrying out bug fixing processes and implementing new functionalities. The software was developed under Laravel framework.

S EDUCATION

=== 2016 - 2018

Portugal

Professional Multimedia Course

Escola Oliveira Júnior

Mean Overall Score: 16 (0-20)

■ 2018 - 2020

Portugal

The cnical Specialization Multimedia

Course

CFPIC

Mean Overall Score: 15 (0-20)

EDUCATION

■ 2020 - 2023

Portugal

Multimedia Bachelor

Instituto Superior Miguel Torga

Mean Overall Score: 14 (0-20)

SKILLS

(i) LANGUAGES

Portuguese

English

Native

Conversational

(i) SOFTWARE SKILLS

Wordpress

HTML, CSS

PHP

Javascript, Node.js, React

SQL

Design

(photoshop, illustrator...)

PROJECTS

Website - Fisioterapia Elsa Martins

■ 06/2022 - 10/2022

https://fisioelsamartins.pt

W Wordpress

■ The project consists of developing a website for the company Fisioterapia Elsa Martins. This website is an online platform for the company to promote its physiotherapy and rehabilitation services, and provide information about the clinic, its team, and its mission.

Website - Redemovel / Arpuro

11/2018 - 02/2019

W Wordpress

https://redemovel.pt

https://arpuro.pt/clima

■ The project consists of developing a website for the company Redemovel and Arpuro. The website will be an online communication and marketing tool for the company, where its customers can learn about its products and services, as well as obtain information about the company and its values.